[{"answer": "I like the dress very much.", "docId": "130121pmt", "aSentId": 11, "question": "Do you like what you saw?", "qSentId": 10}, {"answer": "I think -- you know, we got Alina Cho joining us now.", "docId": "130121pmt", "aSentId": 36, "question": "You know?", "qSentId": 35}, {"answer": "Yes, I do.", "docId": "130121pmt", "aSentId": 38, "question": "Alina, do you know who the designer was on that?", "qSentId": 37}, {"answer": "I mean, I have to be honest, I'm surprised and not surprised.", "docId": "130121pmt", "aSentId": 104, "question": "What do you think?", "qSentId": 103}, {"answer": "No, it's better than that.", "docId": "130121pmt", "aSentId": 155, "question": "As a man who dresses in Jimmy Choo (INAUDIBLE)?", "qSentId": 154}, {"answer": "Well, I -- I just -- I was --", "docId": "130121pmt", "aSentId": 213, "question": "How do you feel about Jimmy Choo shoes?", "qSentId": 212}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "130121pmt", "aSentId": 222, "question": "And Anderson?", "qSentId": 221}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "130121pmt", "aSentId": 254, "question": "Is that right?", "qSentId": 253}, {"answer": "We did it, we did kind of like --", "docId": "130121pmt", "aSentId": 321, "question": "How many were watching your first dance?", "qSentId": 320}, {"answer": "I cannot hear, Piers, at all.", "docId": "130121pmt", "aSentId": 350, "question": "How did you feel?", "qSentId": 349}, {"answer": "It's amazing.", "docId": "130121pmt", "aSentId": 361, "question": "What does that mean to you?", "qSentId": 360}, {"answer": "So help me, God.", "docId": "130121pmt", "aSentId": 420, "question": "So help you, God?", "qSentId": 419}, {"answer": "EE: I think they have to be ready to go.", "docId": "130121pmt", "aSentId": 510, "question": "Are they all geared up and ready to go?", "qSentId": 509}, {"answer": "I reckon he already has them made.", "docId": "130121pmt", "aSentId": 520, "question": "How quickly will he make it and the knock-offs?", "qSentId": 519}, {"answer": "The slow dance was awesome.", "docId": "130121pmt", "aSentId": 538, "question": "What did you think of the slow dance?", "qSentId": 537}, {"answer": "Oh gosh, it is an awesome feeling.", "docId": "130121pmt", "aSentId": 543, "question": "For people at home and they're watching and they're listening, how do you explain?", "qSentId": 542}]